Allied Building Trades Council (Rochester, NY) Records 5877
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Allied Building Trades Council (Rochester, NY) Records
1983-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Allied Building Trades Council
5877
8.5 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records.
5722892
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 13, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 03, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5820 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5822 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Rochester, NY. Records on Microfilm 5816 mf: International Bricklayers, Masons, Plasters, Tilelayers and Terrazzo Workers Local 11 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5852: Allied Building Trades Council of Rochester, NY, Minutes 6239: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 6239 MB: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Memorabilia 6239 AV: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Audio-Visual Materials 6239 P: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Photographs
Building trades -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rochester; Allied Building Trades Council (Rochester, N.Y.)
5722892
- Allied Building Trades Minutes (includes substantial amount of correspondence, notes, etc.), 4/1957-12/1975, 16" (Box 1)
  - Hotel Rochester April 22, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jan 11, 1960 - July 7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jan 5, 1970 - Jan 4, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - July 12, 1971 - Jan 8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - July 2, 1973 - March 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - March 29, 1974 - Jan 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - April 7, 1975 - Oct 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes (includes substantial amount of correspondence, notes, etc.), 1/1976-12/1979, 12" (Box 2)
  - ABT 1/5/76-3/29/76 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ABT 4/5/79 - 8/30/76 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ABT 9/13/76 - 12/27/76 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1/3/77 - 2/28/77 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 3/7/77 - 5/23/77 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 6/6/77 - 10/31/77 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 11/7/77-4/24/78 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 5/1/78 - 8/28/78 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 9/11/78 - 2/26/79 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 3/12/79 - 7/30/79 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 8/6/79 - 12/31/79 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1975-82, 12"; Subject files, 1970s-80s, 4" (Box 3)
  - $750 Million Bond Issue, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - District 50 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Gananda - Wage Appeal (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lisbon Law Suit (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - OGS Bid Info Sheets, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - JT. Bldg. Trades of N.W. PA. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence 4/1 - 12/31, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 1/1 - 3/31, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Clippings, 1970s-90s, 2"; Subject files, 1970s-80s, 8" (Box 4)
  - LeCesse 8/22, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - JEI, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - JEI, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - JEI, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO papers (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - JEI, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - JEI, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Agreements (miscellaneous affiliated local unions), 1970s; Reference files (non-historical) (Box 5)
  - Settlements + Agreements Pamphlets (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets + Agreements (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Reports + Guides (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - reports + Resolutions (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ullico, CETA, etc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1968-74, 6"; Subject files, 1970s, 10" (Box 6)
  - Senate + Assem. Bills, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Senate bills, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Senate + Assembly bills (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wage determinations, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wage Determinations, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Wage Determinations, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - OGS - Bio Info sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - OGS - Bio Info Sheets, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - building trades, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Subject files, 1970s-80s, 16" (Box 7)
  - Pay by Check (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Parcels; OSHA; etc. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pay by Check (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Wage Determinations, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wage Determinations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Wage Determinations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Wage Rate Determinations, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Posted Rates, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jurisdictional Areas of Affiliate (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Directories + Programs (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ballots (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Improvement Programs, Funds (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rochester AFL-CIO (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1983-84, 4"; Subject files, 1970s-80s, 10" (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Wyoming Comm Hospital - Warsaw (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Wage Rate Rulings (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wage Determinations, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Widow + Minor children of Painters Trust (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Comm for Energy Awareness (USCEA) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Symposium on nuclear Energy (JEI) Auburn, NY March 21, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Shirley Bates Reports (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Situs Picketing (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SCOPA (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sonyra Job (Gautieri) Asbestos Problem (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Recruitment for Construction (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Rowntowner Motor Inn (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Rochester Jobs Inc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ramp for Handicapped - City Hall (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Merger - Public works + Labor Standards (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Position Paper (M.C. Recycling) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Endorsement Questionairre (Bd. Comm.) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Political endorsements, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Political endorsements, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NLRB - (D'Angelo + Khan) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Labor workshop April 10, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Life Ins Info (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Light Rail transit (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Labor Reform Law (HR-840) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Labor Law Reform (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hamlin Plaza - income realty (AIMIS) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Marketplace Mall (Henrietta) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Denim Dance June 6, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dimarco (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - C.E.T.A. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Affirmative Actions (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Joint Bldg Trades - Central + W. NY (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Joint Bldg. TR of Central + W NY, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - JT. Bldg. Tr. Of central + W. NY, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Jt. Bldg. Trades - Central + W. NY, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Jt. Bldg. Trades - Central + W. NY, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Jt. Bldg. Trades - Central + W. NY, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)